<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Harlan A Nelson </title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Harlan A Nelson </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>R Packages</title>
      <link>/2021/05/03/r-packages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/05/03/r-packages/</guid>
      <description>  Statistical Model Evaluation performance Provide utilities for computing indices of model quality and goodness of fit.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Methods</title>
      <link>/2021/04/14/research-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/04/14/research-methods/</guid>
      <description> CONSORT 2010 checklist of information to include when reporting a randomised trial  Title and abstract   Identification as a randomised trial in the title
  Structured summary of trial design, methods, results, and conclusions (for specific guidance see CONSORT for abstracts)
  Introduction: Background and Objectives  Scientific background and explanation of rationale. Specific Objecives or hypothesis  Methods  Trial Design  Description of trial design (such as parallel, factorial) including allocation ratio Important changes to methods after trial commencement (such as eligibility criteria), with reasons   Participants  Eligibility criteria for participants Settings and locations where the data were collected    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wyzant: Harlan N.</title>
      <link>/2021/01/11/wyzant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/01/11/wyzant/</guid>
      <description>I do tutoring on Wyzant: The link is Harlan N..</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Proposed for an Image</title>
      <link>/2020/12/29/software-proposed-for-an-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/12/29/software-proposed-for-an-image/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of the software I use every day but is not currently included in my Windows virtual machine image. Note that the VM I log into is Windows.
My goal is to create a docker image with these in it.
 Docker Install the image with all my linux programs.  In the case where Docker is not used, here are the windows progams:
 R: Windows RStudio Download Azure Data Studio  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting the Website Started</title>
      <link>/2020/12/26/getting-the-website-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/12/26/getting-the-website-started/</guid>
      <description> These are the steps I used to get my web site running.
Use RStudio and blogdown to create the computer instructions for the site. Use github to store those computer instructions on the internet Use Netify to host and build the website Use Godaddy to register the domain (would just use any registerar)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git hub and Azure Repository: Person Access Tokens (PAT)</title>
      <link>/2020/12/26/github-and-azure-repos-person-access-tokens-pat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/12/26/github-and-azure-repos-person-access-tokens-pat/</guid>
      <description>Git Hub and Azure Ropository are moving away from passwords to other means of authentication. There are a few ways to authenticate:
 Personal Access Tokens (PAT) embedded in your app.
 Token keys used by SSH. Two step identification. Use of PATs as passwords entered when authentication is needed.  The PATs are used in applications that access accounts such as your repositories. The PAT is stored securely in the app and then used for authentication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo; example website for the blogdown package. The theme was forked from @jrutheiser/hugo-lithium-theme and modified by Yihui Xie.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
